A Finding Aid to the Betty Parsons Gallery records and personal papers, circa 1920-1991, bulk 1946-1983, in the Archives of American Art AAA.parsbett
Archives of American Art
- Artists Files, 1935-1983; Series 1; (Boxes 1-18, 51, and OV 53; 17.8 linear feet)
  - Lindner, Richard - Photograph, Artist, circa 1954-1979; (See box 51) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Lindner, Richard - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1954-1979; (2 folders, see also box 51; not scanned) (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Biographical Material, circa 1947-1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Lipton, Seymour - General, 1947-1963; (7 folders) (Box 10, Folder 12-18)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1950-1963; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Press Releases, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Announcements and Catalogs, 1948-1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Publications, 1951-1962 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Clippings, 1947-1964; (3 folders) (Box 10, Folder 24-26)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Sketches, circa 1947-1963 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Photographs, Artist and Betty Parsons, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Photographs, Installation, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1947-1963; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 10, Folder 30-31)
  - Lipton, Seymour - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1947-1963; (Not scanned) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Little, John, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Lukin, Sven, 1960-1966; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 34-35)
  - Lukin, Sven - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1959-1966; (Not scanned) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Malpass, Michael, 1978-1981; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 37-38)
  - Marfield, Dwight, 1944-1946 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Margo, Boris - General, 1944-1979; (5 folders) (Box 10, Folder 40-44)
  - Margo, Boris - Press Releases, 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Margo, Boris - Announcements and Catalogs, 1946-1964; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 46-47)
  - Margo, Boris - Boris Margo: Graphic Work, 1932-1968, (Partially scanned) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Margo, Boris - Clippings, 1947-1962; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 49-50)
  - Margo, Boris - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1944-1979; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 10, Folder 51-52)
  - Margo, Boris - Photographs, Installation, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Margo, Boris - Photograph, Artist, circa 1944-1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Margo, Boris - Photographs, Artist with Sculpture Commissioned by Hawaii Academy of Art, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Margo, Boris - Reproductions, Works of Art, circa 1944-1979; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Martin, Agnes - Biographical Material, circa 1958-1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Martin, Agnes - General, 1958-1983; (4 folders) (Box 11, Folder 6-9)
  - Martin, Agnes - Announcements and Catalogs, 1958-1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Martin, Agnes - Clippings, 1958-1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Martin, Agnes - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1958-1983; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
  - Martin, Agnes - Photograph, Installation, circa 1958-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Mason, Susan Yardley, 1973-1979; (Partially scanned) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory - Biographical Material, circa 1967-1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory - General, 1967-1979; (3 folders) (Box 11, Folder 17-19)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory - Announcements and Catalogs, 1969-1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory - Clippings, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1967-1979; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - McFadden, Elizabeth, 1956-1975; (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - McFadden, Elizabeth - Photographs, Works of Art, 1956-1975; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Menkin, Marie, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Menkin, Marie - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1949-1951; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Miles, Jeanne, 1943-1966 (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
  - Miller, Guy, undated; (Partially scanned) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Mo, Carlo, 1969; (Partially scanned) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Monasterio, Luis Ortiz, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Murray, Robert - Biographical Material, circa 1963-1970 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Murray, Robert - Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Murray, Robert - Sales and Expenses, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Murray, Robert - Announcements and Catalogs, 1965-1974 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Murray, Robert - Photographs, Installations, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Murray, Robert - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1963-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Murray, Robert - Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1963-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Murray, Robert - Photographs, Works of Art, 1960s; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 40-43)
  - Murray, Robert - Clippings, 1964-1968; (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 44-45)
  - Nelson, Clara Katherine, 1940-1941; (Partially scanned) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Nevelson, Mike, undated; (Partially scanned) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Newman, Barnett - Biographical Material, circa 1950-1980 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Newman, Barnett - Correspondence, 1950-1982; (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 49-50)
  - Newman, Barnett - Sales and Expenses, 1949-1958 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Newman, Barnett - Works in Betty Parsons Collections, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Newman, Barnett - Announcements and Catalogs, 1959-1982 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Newman, Barnett - Clippings, 1950-1971 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Newman, Barnett - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1950-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Nuala (Elsa de Brun) - General, 1970-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Nuala (Elsa de Brun) - Catalogs, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Nuala (Elsa de Brun) - Clippings, 1947-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Nuala (Elsa de Brun) - Photographs, Works of Art, 1970s; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - O'Doherty, Brian (Patrick Ireland), 1969-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - O'Doherty, Brian (Patrick Ireland), Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1969-1975; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1965-1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso - General, 1941-1964; (4 folders) (Box 12, Folder 8-11)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso - Price Lists and List of Collectors, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1941-1964; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso - Photographs, Installations, circa 1941-1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso - Announcements and Catalogs, 1943-1961 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso - Clippings, 1953-1961 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ostergaard, Glenn, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ostergaard, Glenn - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1977-1982; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Owens, Charles - General, 1942-1951; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
  - Owens, Charles - Clippings and Announcements, 1942-1948 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Owens, Charles - Snapshots, Artist, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Owens, Charles - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1942-1951; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 23-25)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - General, 1958-1963; (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 26-28)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - Clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - Announcements and Catalogs, 1958-1963; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - Photographs, Installation, circa 1958-1963 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1958-1963; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1958-1963; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 35-38)
  - Parzini, Luigi, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Pearson, Henry, 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Perry, Charles O., 1964-1974 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Perry, Charles O., 1964-1974; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Biographical Material, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Contracts, 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Writings about Pollock, 1949-1975 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Draft of Chronology for Exhibition Catalog, Museum of Modern Art, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Correspondence, 1947-1983; (6 folders) (Box 12, Folder 47-52)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1948-1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Loans, Consignments, and Lists of Works, 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Advertising, 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Stedelijk Museum Exhibition, 1949-1950; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
  - Pollock, Jackson - The Hilltop Theater Exhibition, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Pollock, Jackson - The Arts Club of Chicago Exhibition, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Betty Parsons Gallery Exhibition (April 9-27, 1983), (3 folders; partially scanned) (Box 13, Folder 8-10)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1979; (Not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Announcements, 1948-1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Catalogs, circa 1951 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Announcements, Duplicates, 1948-1982; (Not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Betty Parsons Private Collection, Catalogs, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Clippings, 1949-1982; (2 folders; see also Box 51) (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Clippings on Betty Parsons Gallery, 1975-1982 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Cancelled Checks, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Miscellaneous Notes and Printed Material, circa 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Photograph, Installation, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Photograph Orders, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Pollock, Jackson - Photographs, Works of Art, 1948-1951; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
  - Porter, Stephen, 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Biographical Material, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Writings by Artist, 1951-1955 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Writings on Artist, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Correspondence, 1948-1983; (3 folders) (Box 13, Folder 29-31)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Appraisals, 1964, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Sales and Expenses, 1948-1971; (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 33-36)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Brasses (rubbings), 1951 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Brasses (rubbings and line drawings), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Lists of Photographs, circa 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Color Separations, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 41-42)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Whitney Museum Retrospective Exhibition (April 17 - May 26, 1963) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Art Journals, 1963, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Art Journals Duplicates, 1963, 1965; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Announcements and Catalogs, 1948-1978; (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 5-7)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Announcements and Catalogs, Duplicates, 1948-1965; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Price Lists, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Gallery Inventories, circa 1950-1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Advertising, 1948-1961 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Clippings, 1949-1974; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard - Photographs, Artist, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Prentice, Nena, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Putnam, Wallace, 1958-1969; (Partially scanned) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Radoczy, Albert, circa 1946 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1951-1983; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert - Photographs, Works of Art, 1951-1983; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Biographical Material, circa 1958-1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Statement on Art, circa 1958-1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Interview with Artist by Peter Selz, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Correspondence, 1957-1980; (7 folders; slides not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 26-32)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Inventories, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Prices Lists, 1958-1970 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Sales and Expenses, 1958-1969 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Political Activities on UC Berkeley Campus, circa 1970 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Announcements and Catalogs, 1959-1969; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 37-38)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Clippings, 1959-1970; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Publications, 1959-1971; (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 41-43)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Lithograph Series, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Lithograph Series, "Hommage a Klee", 1967 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Reichek, Jesse - "Fontis: Poem by Rene Char, Fourteen Engravings by Jesse Reichek" (edition 24 of 25), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Reichek, Jesse - "Fontis: Poem by Rene Char, Fourteen Engravings by Jesse Reichek" (edition 17 of 25), 1961; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1958-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1958-1970; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 2-5)
  - Reichek, Jesse - Photographs, Installations, circa 1958-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Biographical Material, circa 1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Statements on Art, circa 1962 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Correspondence, 1947-1982; (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 9-11)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Price Lists, 1946-1956 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Summary of Sales, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Sales and Expenses, 1946-1977; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Gallery Inventories, 1951-1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Loan Agreements, circa 1963-1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Ad Reinhardt Retrospective, (November 23, 1966 - January 15, 1967: The Jewish Museum, New York, N.Y.) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1947-1967; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Photographs, Installations, 1952-1967 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Photographic Collage of Ad Reinhardt Mural from the 1930s, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Catalogs, 1960-1974 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Announcements, 1947-1980; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - Reinhardt, Ad - Clippings, 1946-1967; (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 26-28)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Biographical Material, circa 1959-1975 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1959-1971 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Announcements, 1959-1971 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Clippings, 1959-1971 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Publicity, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Reynal, Jeanne - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1959-1975; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Richter, Hans - Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Richter, Hans - Announcements and Catalogs, 1968-1983 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Richter, Hans - Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Richter, Hans - Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Richter, Hans - Photograph, Installation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Richter, Hans - Transparency, Work of Art, circa 1973; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Robinson, Alexander, 1947-1957 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Robinson, Alexander - Photographs, Works of Art, 1947-1957; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Rosen, Jim, 1977-1978; (See also OV 53) (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Rothko, Mark - Writings on Art, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Rothko, Mark - Biographical Material, circa 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Rothko, Mark - Mailing List, circa 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Rothko, Mark - Correspondence, 1946-1983 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Rothko, Mark - Gallery Inventories, 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Rothko, Mark - Trial Re: Estate of Mark Rothko, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Rothko, Mark - Appraisal of Rothko Works, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Rothko, Mark - Price Lists, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Rothko, Mark - Sales and Expenses, 1946-1977 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Rothko, Mark - Cancelled Checks, 1950-1953 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Rothko, Mark - Announcements, 1949-1981 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Rothko, Mark - Clippings, 1946-1978 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Rothko, Mark - Color Reproductions of Rothko Works, circa 1946-1952; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Rothko, Mark - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1946-1952; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Rothko, Mark - Photographs, Installations, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Ruchin, Eugen, 1966-1974; (Partially scanned) (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Russo, Sam - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Russo, Sam - Consignments and Sales, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Russo, Sam - Announcements, Catalogs, and Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Russo, Sam - Photographs and Slides, Works of Art, circa 1970-1973; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ryan, Anne - Biographical Material, circa 1954-1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ryan, Anne - Correspondence, 1950-1979; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Ryan, Anne - Sales and Expenses, 1950-1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ryan, Anne - Gallery Inventories and Price Lists, 1950-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ryan, Anne - Clippings, 1951-1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ryan, Anne - Announcements and Catalogs, 1950-1981; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Ryan, Anne - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Schnabel, Day - Biographical Material, circa 1945-1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Schnabel, Day - Correspondence, 1945-1976; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
  - Schnabel, Day - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1946-1957 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Schnabel, Day - Announcements, 1946-1957 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Schnabel, Day - Clippings, 1946-1957 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Schnabel, Day - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1946-1976; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Schnabel, Day - Photographs, Artist at Work, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Biographical Material, circa 1954-1962 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Correspondence, 1954-1969 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Price Lists, 1954-1962 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Sales and Expenses, 1953-1963 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Announcements and Catalogs, 1953-1962 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Clippings, 1953-1962 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1953-1962; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Biographical Material, circa 1951-1971 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Correspondence, 1951-1971 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Sales and Expenses, 1948-1971 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Price Lists, 1951-1957 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Sketches, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Color Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1948-1957; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Announcements and Catalogs, 1951-1967 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Clippings, 1948-1971 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Sekula, Sonia - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1948-1957; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Shemi, Yehiel, 1960-1983 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Sherman, Robert, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Smith, Leon, 1958-1962; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 40-41)
  - Smith, Leon - Photographs, circa 1958-1962; (Partially scanned) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Soffer, Sasson - Biographical Material, circa 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Soffer, Sasson - General, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Soffer, Sasson - Clippings, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Soffer, Sasson - Announcements and Catalogs, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Soffer, Sasson - Photographs, Installation, circa 1961 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Soffer, Sasson - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1960-1964; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 48-49)
  - Somare, Guido, 1960-1965; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 50-51)
  - Somare, Guido - Photographs, Works of Art, 1960-1965; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Biographical Material, 1947-1957 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Correspondence, 1947-1964, 1983; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 54-56)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Sales and Expenses, 1944-1958 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Price Lists and Lists of Work, 1943-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Clippings, 1948-1958; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Other Printed Material, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Announcements and Catalogs, 1943-1959, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - Stamos, Theodoros - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1947-1957; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Stephan, John, 1945-1952; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
  - Stephan, John - Photographs, Works of Art, 1968; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Still, Clyfford - Correspondence, 1947-1960, 1979, 1982; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
  - Still, Clyfford - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Still, Clyfford - Announcements and Clippings, 1947-1980 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Still, Clyfford - Photographs, Installations, circa 1947-1953 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Still, Clyfford - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1949-1969; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Strobel, Thomas, 1964-1965; (Partially scanned) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Sturm, Dorothy - Biographical Material, circa 1956 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Sturm, Dorothy - Correspondence, 1952-1975; (4 folders) (Box 17, Folder 19-22)
  - Sturm, Dorothy - Announcements and Guest Book Sheets, 1955-1961 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Sturm, Dorothy - Catalogs and Clippings, 1955-1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Sturm, Dorothy - Price Lists, Sales, and Expenses, 1952-1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Sturm, Dorothy - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1952-1975; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 26-29)
  - Thomas, John, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Tomlin, Bradley Walker, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Turnbull, William, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Turnbull, William - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1955-1960; (Partially scanned) (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Tuttle, Richard, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Walker, John, 1967-1978 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Wall, Leon, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Wall, Leon - Photographs, Works of Art, 1959; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Wardlaw, George, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Weber, Hugo - Biographical Material, circa 1954-1960 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Weber, Hugo - Correspondence, 1954-1960; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
  - Weber, Hugo - Price Lists, 1954-1959 (Box 17, Folder 42)